<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MyNews</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="list_empty">sorry we could not find any articles matching your search</string>
    <string name="dateFromat">"-"</string>
    <string name="aboutMyNews">MyNews is an application designed by Openclassrooms and developed by its students for the 5th project for the graduation of Android developer. </string>
    <string name="about2">This application uses the API of the news york times so that you can find the articles that interest you</string>
    <string name="findUrl">You can find more information on the site of New york times:</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="help1">When you click on an article, you display the contents of the article.\n</string>
    <string name="help2">A magnifying glass allows you to search all the items in the New York Times database (not the items displayed on the screen).
This one allows to search the articles according to the following criteria:\n</string>
    <string name="help3">When you click on an article, you display the co</string>
    <string name="help4">The list of keywords (required);
The minimum publication date (optional);
The maximum date of publication (optional);
The category or categories (at least one category must be checked).</string>
    <string name="help5">The list of keywords (required);
The minimum publication date (optional);
The maximum date of publication (optional);
The category or categories (at least one category must be checked).
On validation, the results are displayed on a new screen, in the form of a list (as on the home screen). If no result is found, indicate it with a pop-up.\n</string>
    <string name="help6">Notifications
To avoid missing any relevant news, you decide to add a feature to warn you when a new article is published,
        according to criteria that you have predefined. To do this, you decide to add a new settings screen,
        accessible from the menu point of the main screen of the application.\n</string>
    <string name="help7">If notifications are enabled, then the app will check once a day if news matches the search criteria, then notify you with a notification message.
In the menu at the top left, you can choose the categories that interest you. Once a category is selected, the items are displayed.</string>
    <string name="arts">Arts</string>
    <string name="business">Business</string>
    <string name="sciences">Sciences</string>
    <string name="politics">Politics</string>
    <string name="sports">Sports</string>
    <string name="travel">Travel</string>
    <string name="search_query_terms">Search query terms</string>
    <string name="enable_notifications">Enable notifications (once par day)</string>
    <string name="begin_date">Begin date</string>
    <string name="end_date">End date</string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="categories">Catégories</string>
    <string name="sections">Sections :</string>
    <string name="techno">Technology</string>
    <string name="autos">Automobiles</string>
    <string name="params">Params</string>
    <string name="notification">Notifications</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>


</resources>
